

MONIKA PATEL

ABOUT ME

Outgoing developer and thinking outside the box to determine and deliver outstanding results + 3 years of experience in Microsoft technologies. Seeking to leverage my interpersonal skills to bring a solid Software Developer perspective to the position. To know more about me please visit my website monikapatel.info

CONTACT ME

(+64) 221379800 monikapatel.it@outlook.com

> Flat 3, 4 Patterson Street Sandrinaham Auckland

EXPERIENCES

Software Developer SCANTECH LTD

Feb 2015 - Present

- Design and implement data entry win Forms software for document digitalizing.
- Started from bottom to top to understand data entry software to refactored module & abstract database queries.
- Supported codifying to amazon web services.
- Designed and implemented new features across system structures and interface.
- Improve performance and reduced operational cost by architectural codes and SLA report usage

Front End Developer ACE RENTALS CAR Aug 2014 – Oct 2014

- Redesign new features across front end for rental car portal & email marketing.
- Agile-style collaboration with marketing manager, business analyst and database developer

Software Developer TATVASOFT LTD Jan 2014 - May 2014

- Full-stack web development, in collaboration with a project manager, UI designer and fellow teammates.
- Scouted as intern eventually offered full-time permanent role within a short while.
- Implemented prototype UI design for insurance service during requirement analysis phase; accepted as a final design.

SELECTED PROJECTS

MonikaPatel.info PERSONAL PORTFOLIO

Design personal portfolio CV web app in pure CSS/HTML

ACE Rentals Car ACE RENTALS CAR

- Redesign rental car portal website for Australia and New Zealand client.
- Set up Analytics tracking Google API account.
- Photoshop Marketing strategies
- Design email layout for Email marketing

Insurox TATVASOFT LTD

- Designed and implemented insurance service website for the U.S. based client, including content management system (MNC)
- Participated in all the phases of SDLC for software development.
- Primary code utilization: C#, SQL, MVC, Entity framework, HTML/CSS, JavaScript/jQuery

EDUCATION

B.S. In Computer Science CHAROTAR UNIVERSITY

- Ranked: 8 of 120 (TOP 5%)
- GPA: 8.5
- Awarded placement with in MNC(TATVASOFT LTD)







